ocado
se
ano
ah ah ah ah
me
Soooo...
what's this?
The game is on me!
I look forward to working with you today
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you
Please take care of the show
Please take care of me.
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please...
We had some time before the show.
I had some miso soup from the caterer.
Miso soup
I'd like to have some miso soup.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
Itadakimasu
Miso soup
Wow, it looks delicious!
No way.
Takato.
Onigiri and miso soup is the best
But that miso soup...
It's mine.
I saw it in a foreign TV show.
That miso soup is mine
Hey!
That's not mine?
I think it's time for some miso soup.
I'm almost there.
Foreign drama.
So I'll have some.
It's so good!
I want onigiri, too.
I'm sure they'd go well together.
What kind of onigiri would you like?
Salmon.
Here you go.
Salmon onigiri.
Bon appétit!
It's huge!
Wow!
Bon appétit!
Salmon onigiri!
Mmm.
Mmm. - Mmm.
Nori.
Rice.
Salmon, all good.
It's the best of three worlds.
All three in one onigiri.
The best!
So I'd like to have some miso soup!
I'd like to have some miso soup!
Bon appétit!
Abura-age and tofu
Oh, no!
Oh no!
This stings
I'm still in the middle of the show.
If I eat this between part 1 and 2
I might cry.
It's so comforting.
Miso soup is the best thing I've ever had while fishing.
but the second best is this.
I carry a lot of stuff when I go fishing.
I also bring coffee.
Coffee is really good when you're outdoors.
It's really good!
I recently started solo camping.
I have an errand to run.
I'm like...
It's more like...
It's not so much the ingredients, but the soup.
I like to have a lot of soup.
Miso soup is...
I like the ingredients, of course, but...
But for now...
I think the soup is too much.I thought there was too much juice.
The timing.
The timing is right.
The timing... the timing... the timing...
You can take it with you.
I'm off.
I met Louie the other day.
It was crazy at first.
Really?
He was swimming so fast.
I didn't know if she'd be okay.
But I was nice to her.
And then suddenly, Louie came up behind me...
And then suddenly...
He put his hand on my shoulder and licked it.
He was licking his lips.
And then he put his hand on my mouth.
I think he's a crafty guy, Louie.
I love crafts.
You ever take a picture of him?
When he eats good food.
You're so proud of yourself.
Because when I came here, I didn't get a single picture of you.
You're right.
That's for sure.
That's why I'm the one...
When I say, "Come here," you're never in the picture.
He only goes to his sister.
Not even to sit down.
Sit.
But I did it once.
I was like...
I'm going to drink some miso soup to power up.
I'm going to take on the challenge of the live show!
Goo Touch
Round One Shuffle
Thank you very much!
It's called "Round One Shuffle".
We're going to start with round one.
We're going to have a meeting to speak up.
Let's speak out together.
Shouting out to each other
in good harmony.
For today's concert
I want to do my best
And
Two new songs
Miss Android and After School Gyutto
and "After School Gutto".
Yes, that's right.
I'm still a little nervous, but
I'm looking forward to it.
It's our first show.
To make an impression
I'll give it my all.
I'll do my best.
Hi, I'm Ryouto Nakano.
Today is the Round One Shuffle in Tokyo.
Thank you very much!
We're going to open the show in two parts.
I don't know if it's the live show itself or the one-man show itself.
The live itself, or rather, the one-man show itself
It's been a while since I've had a one-man show.
It's been quite a while since I've had a one-man show.
This time, I'm going to do my voice again.
I'm very happy to say that this is the first time I've done a live performance in the past.
Thank you very much!
These times are getting calmer and calmer
and we are moving forward.
we can also speak out.
Haraji Department itself
We have never had a one-man show where we had to speak out.
so I'm really looking forward to today's show.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to the live performance that I'm going to make with all of you.
I hope I can make a live performance with you all
I'm really looking forward to it.
And this time, I'll be performing two new songs for the first time.
we are going to perform two new songs for the first time
featuring Mr. Android
Itsuki and After School Gyutto
We are going to perform these two songs.
Mr. Android's song is
Android is a song featuring Mr. Itsuki.
In the soundtrack, Itsuki is singing
Itsuki sings about half of the original part, butI'm singing about half of the original part of the song.
But this time it's a live version.
It is a live version, so the part sung by Itsuki-san is also sung by
This time, it's a live version, so the part sung by Itsuki is also sung by the original members.
I would like you to pay attention to the live version.
I hope you'll pay attention to that too.
Houkago Gyutto also has a music video and a tie-up
It's a song that's played in many places.
It's a song that is played in many places.
The choreography of the song
In the music video, we only dance the chorus.
so the other parts of the song are also quite cute and unique.
There are a lot of cute and unique
There are a lot of cute and unique choreographies.
I hope you will pay attention to it.
And I'm looking forward to hearing from the observers.
I'm looking forward to it.
So it's almost time for the show.
I'm going to do my best with the six of us plus Kazu.
I'll do my best.
Hello everyone, this is Takashi Okura.
Today is April 14th.
LOUD & SHUFFLE!
I'm in front of a part of it now.
But this time...
What can I say?
It's a one-man show.
It's the first time you've performed out loud.
Yes.
It's called "Unveiling Live".
And the title?
LOUD & SHUFFLE.
What's the "shuffle" part?
I'm curious about that.
But before that, we are going to perform two new songs today.
Mr. Android and After School Cute.
This is Mr. Android.
Android and Houkago Kyutto (After School Cute).
Android and
A little glimpse into
the heart of a person
This part of the song is well choreographed
The choreography is faithfully reproduced.
And then there's the "Mr." part.
This is the kind of
Mr. feeling
Mr. feeling.
In After School Cute, it's like this.
of youth
After school, after school
the image of after school
The tune is up-tempo and
It is a song that makes you excited and happy
It's also a song that makes you happy.
After all, it is a tie-up with Duel Masters
Duel Masters tie-up
In this way
I hope this song will be a hit with the
the age of the people who watch Duel Masters.
The choreography is tailored to the age range of the people who watch Duel Masters.
The choreography is designed to make little kids want to imitate it.
so please look forward to it!
That's all for now.
Loud & Shuffle Part 1
I'll do my best for the first part.
Loud & Shuffle
The Tokyo show is today!
From now on...
It's a live performance.
A live performance where you can speak out.
For us, it's the first time to do it.
I can say that this is the first time
We've never had a show like this before.
You know...
I wanted the audience to sing along with me.
or dance with us.
The choreography...
I hope we can do that together today.
We're going to play two new songs.
This is the first time for us to perform them live.
Mr. Android
Houkago Gyutto (After School Gyutto)
Let's see what kind of songs they are first.
I hope you all enjoy them.
I hope you all enjoy it.
After School Gutto
The 3,3,7 time signature during the interlude.
Lots of danceable parts.Lots of places to dance.
I think it's going to be fun
I hope we can really have fun with all the observers today together
I hope we can have fun!
I'll do my best.
Hello.
This is Yoshida Akanabu.
So, today is the
Loud & Shuffle Tokyo performance
The best part of the show is that it's our first live performance!
The best part of the day is that it's the first time for us to show off our voices in a live performance!
It's the first time for us to show our voices.
It's the first time for us.
We've been doing this for 3 years now.
It's the first time for me to speak out.
So I'm very excited about it.
I'm also looking forward to it.
From now on.
With the observers
I'm looking forward to working with you, the observers
how we can make our voices heard and create a live show together.
I'm very happy to be able to think about how we can make our voice and create a live concert together
I'm having a lot of fun.
I feel that we still have a lot of fun things ahead of us.
I think there will be a lot of fun things in the future
I can think that there will be a lot of fun things in the future when we are still a group.
I can think that there are many fun things to come in the future.
Well, I don't know what will happen at the live
We still don't know what will happen at the show.
We don't know what will happen at the show yet, but
but I hope we can enjoy it together.
And today...
Mr. Android and Hookah Go Get!
in front of the audience for the first time.
I don't know...
After listening to the song...
I'm kind of in love with Mr. Android.
Hookah Go Get!
It's more like...
I mean, it's more like a skille...
It's that kind of song.
but when it's performed
the atmosphere changes drastically.
and there are places where we can have fun together.
I can enjoy it together.
I hope you enjoy these two songs as well.
Cherish the day!
Well, since it's the first performance
I hope we can do our best.
Above all, I hope we can have fun together.
I hope we can have fun together.
I'll do my best.
So today...
The staff will be performing in Tokyo!
Yay!
Today is
It's the first time
It's the first live performance where we don't have to use our voices.
A one-man show.
It's been a long time coming.
We've been waiting a long time.
I think it's the one we've been waiting for.
We're still getting used to it.
But let's get used to it together.
Also...
We'll be performing two new songs.
I'm a little nervous about them too.
I think it's very important to have a good image of our voice.
I'd like to show you what I'm talking about.
I'll do my best.
This is where it all starts.
Our story.
Lesson?
Today... what we're going to do...
For now, I'm just trying to connect with you.
I'm going to say something nice.
Today...
A song? A song.
The dancing part.
I'm gonna sing with you.
I'm going to teach you.
I'm going to teach you so much that you'll finish it today.
Let's make it fun
So that
I'm going to make it so that everyone can remember
Let's make a good impression
Let's make it a good one
Let's have some fun ourselves.
Let's go!
First of all, let's be cheerful.
We'll take a shot.We got one.
Yay!
It's good to have seven people on the radio.
We'll be fine.
We'll be
go our own way
in the city
I don't think there will be a tomorrow
Free hugs
Until now
Of all the crafts and hugs I've given
I've had the most serene hugs.
My heart rate
I think it's going down.
You're the one who's going up.
You're sharing.
You got it.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
What's the matter with you?
It's just... it's just...
You're stronger now.
Yeah.
Somehow.
That's the way
I crossed it.
Thank you.
Thank you all for remembering this.
Thank you for dancing with us.
It's been a lot of fun.
Keep it up.
We'll be touring and dancing.
You're all dancing, too.
That's all for now. Ten years of games.
Thank you so much for today.
Congratulations!
Round & Shuffle Tokyo show part 1 is over!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you very much for your hard work
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was really different from usual.
You said you were OK to speak out.
It was really different.
It was a really different live performance.
It's different.
It's the first time for me to do a one-man show.
It was my first one-man show where I was allowed to speak out
I was surprised that the observers
to speak up.
I was so happy to hear them speak out so positively.
I was so happy.
So I hope we won't lose to them.
we'll keep going forward from here.
The second part of the tour, Osaka, and the summer tour
I'm getting more and more excited!
As it gets bigger and bigger
I'm sure you'll be able to hear the great voices
I'm sure we'll be able to hear them.
Isn't it getting better and better?
Your stomach is getting bigger and bigger
It's getting bigger and bigger.
It's not good.
By then...
I'd like to perfect our voice and all that.
I hope we can perfect it at this live performance.
Let's do our best at the other shows.
We'll do our best.
No, no, no, no.
I can't wait to see the movie.
Wow, what a surprise!
There's a camera here.
Okay, so...
The first show of Loud & Shuffle is over, isn't it?
The first part of the Tokyo show is over!
And then the second part of the show...
It's the break time before the show starts...
How was the first part of the show?
I didn't know that the observers were so vocal.
I didn't know they could be so vocal.
I was surprised.
If we've never experienced it before...
I'm sure you have never experienced something like that before.
I don't think you've ever done it before.
What a performance!
It's really amazing!
And we're only 3.37 seconds away.
And they're all studying.
And we're like...
We'll be right there.
Here! and they'll give it back to us.
Everybody.Everybody.
I can hear you from there even if you have your earpiece on.
I can really hear you.
They're all putting it out there.
I feel like the space we create with the local team and the observers
I feel like the space we create together
I feel like that.
Next time, I'm going to do this LOUD & JUFFLE
I'd like you to do it when you perform that song
I'd like you to do it again when you perform that song outside of this LOUD & JUFFLE.
Yes, I do.
Next time, there will be two parts.
We'll do what we can do.
We'll do what we can to create the best space for the second part as well.
We'll do our best for the second part too!
And that's the end of the first part.
Thank you very much!
It was really the first one-man show
It was the first one-man show.
but everyone did their best to speak up and show us their love
And we were more than happy to hear their love for us.
I was more than happy to hear that.
I am looking forward to more and more live shows in the future.
I'm really looking forward to the future live shows
I'm really looking forward to the future live shows.
I'm imagining so many things.
I wonder what it will be like.
I'm looking forward to it more and more
Assuming that the cause is me
I wonder if this year will be the year when I can become even bigger and better.
I think this year is going to be a year for me to become even bigger and better.
I'm going to do my best in the second part as well.
Let's all speak out together!
Talking about the second part
Letting the younger ones fill the soup
He's a bad guy.
I want some soup, too.
I don't know what to do anymore
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I want it with rice.
I don't want to be bullied
No, I want to do it in the sun
It's hard to take it with me
It's so hot
I'm scared
I wonder why Ryo-san is doing mouth mushrooms
Mouth mushrooms...
All dogs can do it.
I'm filming.
It's a camera scene.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That's it.
That's my boss's house.
It's warming up.
I can't stop wishing.
You wish for it.
Good.
You wish upon it.
What? What was that? Oh, it's me.
Yeah, it's me.
We're playing two shows in a row.
I'm still tired.
But it's when you're tired that you can perform.
We want to be able to perform when we're tired.
I want to be the one who can perform.
Heh heh heh heh
All right, let's raise our spirits
Let's work hard!
Yes!
I'm looking forward to it.
Craft Diary
Nice to meet you.
Someone's coming.
I'll see you on the night of the resurrection.
Nice to meet you.
Well, well, well... it's okay if you do it just for the hell of it.
We're all on the call
Let's do the rhythm of the music
Don't dance, just say it
Let's go!
Like, like, like, like
Let's do it
Like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like.
like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like like likeSimilar, similar, similar.
Come on, let's go.
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
That's it. Round and shuffle.
Thank you so much for your time today.
For your voices and
With your dancing
I really had a great time
I was able to have a really good time!
That's all, Gain was on his own.
Thank you so much for today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It's called a live voice out.
I'd like to hear from you, the observers.
You've been the first liberal since the poll on thoughts.
Yes, you're right.
I haven't heard that since the soda fountain.
Yes, how was it?
Oh, my God, guests.
This is the kind of voice I was expecting to hear.
The observers
Surprisingly, the observers were very vocal.
I was very moved by their willingness to speak up.
I was so happy.
I knew that you had been waving the pen-la with all your might.
I could feel that you had been waving the pen-la with all your might.
but when I hear your voice like this
I felt my heart tremble.
I was so happy to hear your voice.
Above all
I realized for the first time that if I asked him something like this, he would respond
I realized for the first time
We were able to perform live together.
I had only heard soda water.
But you came back.
I was so happy, wasn't I?
It's not just our feelings, but also our voices.
I think it's going to be a great space
I think it's going to be a great space.
I'm looking forward to Osaka.
I'll be at Gorilla Hall on the 28th.
The set ring has been changed.
Please check it out as well!
That's all for now, the game is up to me!
See you in Osaka!
Well, LOUD&SHUFFLE's Tokyo show is over!
Thank you very much!
We had a two-part show today.
It's been a while since we've had a show.
It's been a while since the fall tour.
It's the first one-man show since the fall tour.
It's been a long time.
And this time
I was allowed to speak out since it was LOUD.
It's not so easy.
It was the first time.
I was so surprised.
Thank you all for coming out!
And this time, SHUFFLE was there too.
I'm a pervert.
Weird.
All kinds of things.
Songs sung by...
SHUFFLE.
We would sing songs that are usually sung by seven of us, and then two of us would sing them together.
Or dancing in the background while two sing.
You can do that today.
And what's more, this time the MC is...
You mean they're doing it this time, too?
I was so surprised.
It's not often that you get to do it once or twice.
It doesn't happen very often.
It's because it's a one-time-only show.
I think it was the only time we could do it.
I think it was a really good show.
Next time, LOUD&SHUFFLE will be at Gorilla Hall in Osaka
May 28th at Gorilla Hall in Osaka.
We look forward to seeing you there too!
Thank you very much!
Bye-bye!